<story-context id=".bmad/bmm/workflows/4-implementation/story-context/template" v="1.0">
  <metadata>
    <epicId>1</epicId>
    <storyId>5</storyId>
    <title>Basic Browser Compatibility & Responsiveness</title>
    <status>drafted</status>
    <generatedAt>2025-12-09</generatedAt>
    <generator>BMAD Story Context Workflow</generator>
    <sourceStoryPath>docs/sprint-artifacts/1-5-basic-browser-compatibility-responsiveness.md</sourceStoryPath>
  </metadata>

  <story>
    <asA>a user</asA>
    <iWant>to access QuizZum from common web browsers and devices</iWant>
    <soThat>I can use the tool without compatibility issues</soThat>
    <tasks>
- [ ] **Task 1: Implement Responsive Design (AC: 2)**
  - [ ] Subtask 1.1: Use Chakra UI's responsive features to ensure the layout adapts to mobile, tablet, and desktop screen sizes.
  - [ ] Subtask 1.2: Test the application on various mobile device emulators and real devices.
- [ ] **Task 2: Cross-browser Testing (AC: 1)**
  - [ ] Subtask 2.1: Test the application on the latest stable versions of Chrome, Edge, Firefox, Brave, and Opera.
  - [ ] Subtask 2.2: Document and fix any browser-specific rendering or functionality issues.
    </tasks>
  </story>

  <acceptanceCriteria>
1.  Given QuizZum is accessed via the latest stable versions of Chrome, Edge, Firefox, Brave, and Opera on desktop, when I interact with the application, then all UI elements function as expected.
2.  Given QuizZum is accessed on a mobile device, when I interact with the application, then the UI layout adjusts appropriately and remains usable.
  </acceptanceCriteria>

  <artifacts>
    <docs>
      <doc>
        <path>docs/prd-QuizZum-2025-12-05.md</path>
        <title>QuizZum - Product Requirements Document</title>
        <section>Functional Requirements</section>
        <snippet>FR-019: (MVP) The application functions on the latest stable versions of Google Chrome, Microsoft Edge, Mozilla Firefox, Brave, and Opera on desktop.
FR-020: (MVP) The application is fully responsive across various screen sizes (desktop, tablet, mobile).</snippet>
      </doc>
      <doc>
        <path>docs/architecture.md</path>
        <title>Architecture</title>
        <section>Platform Support</section>
        <snippet>Browser Matrix: Latest stable versions of Google Chrome, Microsoft Edge, Mozilla Firefox, Brave, and Opera on desktop.
Responsive Design: The application should be fully responsive and function well across various screen sizes (desktop, tablet, mobile).</snippet>
      </doc>
      <doc>
        <path>docs/ux-design-specification.md</path>
        <title>QuizZum UX Design Specification</title>
        <section>Responsive Strategy</section>
        <snippet>QuizZum will be built with a thoughtful, adaptive responsive strategy to ensure a visually great and fully functional experience across all devices</snippet>
      </doc>
      <doc>
        <path>docs/epics-QuizZum-2025-12-05.md</path>
        <title>QuizZum - Epic Breakdown</title>
        <section>Story 1.5: (MVP) Basic Browser Compatibility & Responsiveness</section>
        <snippet>User Story: As a user, I want to access QuizZum from common web browsers and devices, so that I can use the tool without compatibility issues.</snippet>
      </doc>
    </docs>
    <code>
      <file>
        <path>frontend/src/app/layout.tsx</path>
        <action>Modify</action>
        <reason>Adjust global layout and styles for responsiveness.</reason>
      </file>
      <file>
        <path>frontend/src/styles/globals.css</path>
        <action>Modify</action>
        <reason>Add or modify global styles for cross-browser compatibility.</reason>
      </file>
      <file>
        <path>frontend/src/components/*</path>
        <action>Modify</action>
        <reason>Adjust individual components for responsiveness and browser compatibility.</reason>
      </file>
    </code>
    <dependencies>
      <ecosystem>
        <name>Node.js (frontend)</name>
        <package>
          <name>react</name>
          <version>latest</version>
        </package>
        <package>
          <name>next</name>
          <version>latest</version>
        </package>
        <package>
          <name>@chakra-ui/react</name>
          <version>latest</version>
        </package>
        <package>
          <name>@emotion/react</name>
          <version>latest</version>
        </package>
        <package>
          <name>@emotion/styled</name>
          <version>latest</version>
        </package>
        <package>
          <name>framer-motion</name>
          <version>latest</version>
        </package>
      </ecosystem>
      <ecosystem>
        <name>Python (backend)</name>
        <package>
          <name>fastapi</name>
          <version>latest</version>
        </package>
        <package>
          <name>uvicorn</name>
          <version>latest</version>
        </package>
        <package>
          <name>python-multipart</name>
          <version>latest</version>
        </package>
      </ecosystem>
    </dependencies>
  </artifacts>

  <constraints>
      <constraint>The application must be responsive and function correctly on the latest stable versions of Chrome, Edge, Firefox, Brave, and Opera.</constraint>
      <constraint>Use Chakra UI's built-in responsive design features where possible.</constraint>
      <constraint>Manual testing across different browsers and devices is required.</constraint>
    </constraints>
  <interfaces>
      <!-- No new interfaces for this story -->
    </interfaces>
  <tests>
      <standards>
        Manual testing across different browsers and devices is crucial for this story. Automated E2E tests can be written to cover the most critical user flows on a primary browser like Chrome.
      </standards>
      <locations>
        - Google Chrome (latest stable)
        - Microsoft Edge (latest stable)
        - Mozilla Firefox (latest stable)
        - Brave (latest stable)
        - Opera (latest stable)
        - Mobile devices (iOS and Android)
      </locations>
      <ideas>
        - Verify that the layout adapts correctly to different screen sizes (mobile, tablet, desktop).
        - Verify that all UI elements are functional and styled correctly on all supported browsers.
        - Verify that there are no JavaScript errors in the console on any of the supported browsers.
      </ideas>
    </tests>
</story-context>
